[{"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, I know who he is.  You're not my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "It's at the jeweler", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm not sending you the bill", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Stop it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, yeah, you make money", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I have money. I make money", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't think I make money. That's what you think isn't it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You don't think I make money. That's what you think isn't it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes you do. That's what you both think", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes you do. That's what you both think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm paying", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Hey, Mrs. my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He's got like a chemical imbalance. He needs to be on medication", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend!", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He's joking", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well you must have done something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Doesn't like you? How can anyone not like you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You know, it seems impossible", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Ma, I know this may be hard for you to understand but I am sure there are many people who do not like me", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't know. They're backed up", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Where'd I take it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": ". . . I threw it in the garbage can on the street. It didn't keep good time. My parents gave it to me so don't mention it again, okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "All right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, we'll just see", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes we will", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I know you did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "So good for you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "So good for you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "We'll you're repeating everything I'm saying", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "We'll you're repeating everything I'm saying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well my friend,,. . . .", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Okay, Mr. my friend, please come this way. We need some ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Leave it. ", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "my friend eh? Pasto costillo homiga ", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What tell? What's a tell", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What tell? What's a tell", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Um, uh, who's it going with, uh, my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "And how often have you been seeing, . . .? I'm sorry what is his name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes, his name", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Are you afraid to tell me his name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "It doesn't matter if you don't see how. I see how", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I want you to tell this young man to give me a call. It is very important that I speak to him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wallet.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You can do it and you will do it", "qsentId": 48}]